Local 1199 Additional Videos 5984 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Additional Videos
1981-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 National Health and Human Service Employees Union (NHHSEU)
5984 AV
3.11 cubic feet
3.1 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
5745649
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 21, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 24, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6209 AV: 1199SEIU Audio-Visual Materials 6140 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings 6169 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 5929 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials
Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199; Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union; Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union. Local 1199 Hospital and Health Care Union (New York, N.Y.)
5745649
- 3/2 event - Washington, D.C., 1 (Box 1)
- Restoring employees rights is good for America, 1993; 2 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  The Campaign for Employee Rights; A Joint Project of 1199 and the National Rainbow Coalition (1993)
- The Battle is over But the war goes on!, 3 (Box 1)
  Hotel Workers Union Local 26
- Dennis Rivera/Local 1199, 1993; 4 (Box 1)
  Sunday edition; WCBS-TV (CBS) New York; April 4, 1993; 11:00-12:00 PM
- Glen Pearcy Productions - AFSCME: 1199 and AFSCME Rallies 2/91, 1991; 5 (Box 1)
  2/13/1991
- Dennis Rivera/Local 1199, 1992; 6 (Box 1)
  Channel 11 News at ten; WPIX-TV (Ind) New York; July 13,, 1992, 10:00-11:00 PM; News 4 New York; WNBC-TV (NBC) New York; July 13, 1992, 11:00-11:35 PM
- Assembly Speaker "Assembly Update": Mel Miller, 1989; 7 (Box 1)
  (D) -- 44th assembly district -- 5/30/1989
- Unlabeled, 8 (Box 1)
- Hospital Strike, 1989; 9 (Box 1)
  WNBC-TV News at 6:31 PM, 10/4/1989; WNBC-TV News at 6:33 PM, 10/4/1989
- Convention Meeting - Jan. 21st, 1989, 10 (Box 1)
  P.S. 87
- Labor X "1199", 11 (Box 1)
- Unlabeled, 12 (Box 1)
- Dennis Rivera - MacNeil-Lehrer (Dec. 11, 1990), 13 (Box 1)
- Greater than the might of Armies, 14 (Box 1)
  Local 1199 video
- Still going strong: the retired members of Local 1199, 16 (Box 1)
- Bill Lynch, New York City Deputy Mayor, 1992; 17 (Box 1)
  Sunday Edition (Syn); WCBS-TV (CBS) New York; August 9, 1992; 11:00-12:00 PM
- Dennis Rivera/Local 1199, 1992; 18 (Box 1)
  Channel 11 News at Ten; WPIX-TV (IND) New York; June 10, 1992; 10:00-11:00 PM; Noticias; WXTV-TV (IND) New York; June 10, 1992; 6:00-6:30 PM
- Medicaid Cuts/Protest, 1995; 19 (Box 1)
  Local New York and Cable Coverage; March 1, 1995 (Schedule Enclosed)
- Medicare cuts/Dennis Rivera, 1995; 20 (Box 1)
  News 4 New York; WNBC-TV (NBC) New York; February 28, 1995; 6:00-6:30 PM
- Local 1199 Protest New York Downtown Hospital, 1981; 21 (Box 1)
  October 29, 1981; Local New York, Network coverage (Schedule enclosed)
- Dennis Rivera/Local 1199, 1995; 22 (Box 1)
  Hourly news; New York 1 Cable; January 26, 1995; 6:00-7:00 PM ET
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 23 (Box 1)
  Channel 9 News; WWOR-TV (IND) New York; June 15, 1992; 10:00-11:00 PM
- Coalition of Conscience, 24 (Box 1)
  John Rowe, MD/Dennis Rivera (1199); Mt. Sinai MC NYC NY; Medical Education/Video Services; School of Medicine
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 25 (Box 1)
  Best Talk on Location; WPIX-TV (IND) New York; March 19, 1992; 9:30-10:00 AM
- Dennis Rivera, 1199, 1992; 26 (Box 1)
  Visiones; WNBC-TV (NBC) New York; May 31, 1992; 8:00-8:30 PM
- Heimi Rivera Mendoza, 1993; 27 (Box 1)
  Presidential Inauguration; CBS-TV Network; January 20, 1993; 1:30 PM
- To Dream, 1 (Box 2)
  1199
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1994; 2 (Box 2)
  New York One News; New York One; February 22, 1994; 11:00-11:30 ET
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 3 (Box 2)
  News Forum; WNBC-TV (NBC) New York; May 24, 1992; 11:30-12:00 PM
- Morris and Carrick Inc. - 1199 - A Call to Action, 1994; 4 (Box 2)
  3/7/1994
- LRA's 14th Annual Labor Awards Dinner, 5 (Box 2)
  Labor Research Association
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1993; 6 (Box 2)
  Hourly News; New York, 1 News; February 19, 1993; 6:00-7:00 AM ET
- Health Care Crisis: We're Fighting, 1989; 7 (Box 2)
  April 11, 1989
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 8 (Box 2)
  Democratic Convention; C-Span; July 15, 1992; 3:00 PM
- Jesse Jackson, 1993; 9 (Box 2)
  Rush Limbaugh (Syndicated); WNYW-TV (FOX) New York; February 17, 1993; 11:00-11:30 AM
- Bronx Lebanon Hospital: 1989 Fund Raiser, 10 (Box 2)
- Manifestation de la CSN a Pointe-Au-Pic, 11 (Box 2)
  87/05/30, CFJP, Grand Journal; 87/05/30, CFTM, Ici Montreal; 87/05/30, CBMT, News watch; 87/05/30, CFCF, Pulse; 87/05/30, CBFT, Tele journal
- Local 1199 Endorses Jerry Brown, 1992; 12 (Box 2)
  March 29-31, 1992; Local New York Coverage (Schedule Enclosed)
- Convention meeting - Jan. 21st, 1989, 1987; 13 (Box 2)
  P.S. 87 (tape 2)
- Looking ahead Civil Liberties in the Future, 14 (Box 2)
  ACLU, Public Education Department
- Convention Meeting - Jan. 21st, 1989, 15 (Box 2)
  P.S. 87 (tape 1)
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 16 (Box 2)
  New York Close Up; New York 1 News; December 23, 1992; 11:15-12:15 PM ET
- Shows 209 and 210, 17 (Box 2)
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 18 (Box 2)
- Betsy McCaughey, 1995; 19 (Box 2)
  Sunday Edition; WCBS-TV (CBS) New York; January 22, 1995; 11:00-12:00 PM
- unlabeled, 20 (Box 2)
- Metroview - Dennis Rivera, 21 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 22 (Box 2)
- Eyewitness News Conference - 2/17/1992, 23 (Box 2)
- President Local 1199 - Manifestation, 24 (Box 2)
  Health Care Albany; From Gerard Toussaint
- Morris and Carrick, 1199 Principles, 1994; 1 (Box 3)
  3/29/1994
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 2 (Box 3)
  Democratic Convention; C-Span; July 15, 1992 - 3:00 PM
- Dennis Rivera/Local 1199, 1995; 3 (Box 3)
  Eyewitness News Conference; WABC-TV (ABC) New York; January 22, 1995; 12:30-1:00 PM; Sunday Edition; WCBS-TV (CBS) New York; January 29, 1995 - 11:00-12:00 PM
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 4 (Box 3)
  Visions; WXTV-TV (IND) New York; June 11, 1992
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 5 (Box 3)
  Charlie Rose; WNET-TV (PBS) New York; December 15, 1992 -- 11:00-12:00 AM
- Hospital Strike in Greenport Long Island, 1993; 6 (Box 3)
  Local New York Coverage; July 1-5, 1993 (Schedule Enclosed)
- Contract Negotiations, Local 1199, 1989; 7 (Box 3)
  Cardinal O'Connor's Show; WCBS/TV; 10/1/1989 - 7;30 AM; William Abelow; News Makers - 10/1/1989
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 8 (Box 3)
  Democratic Convention; CBS-TV Network; July 15, 1992 -- 10:00-11:00 PM ET
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 9 (Box 3)
  Eyewitness News; WABC-TV (ABC) New York; June 11, 1992 -- 6:00-6:30 PM
- 1199 Channel 2 Newscast, 1987; 10 (Box 3)
  1199 Guild Division; Delegate Assembly -- 10/8/1987
- Dennis Rivera/Local 1199, 1992; 11 (Box 3)
  Noticias; WXTV-TV (IND) New York; February 7, 1992 -- 11:00-12:00 PM
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199/Democratic Convention, 1992; 12 (Box 3)
  Democratic Convention Coverage; PBS-TV Network; July 14, 1992 -- 7:00-11:30 PM ET
- Nurses walk out, 1992; 13 (Box 3)
  Daytime Edition; News 12 Long Island; December 22, 1992 -- 9:00-10:00 AM
- Emergency Coalition to Save New York's Health Care, 14 (Box 3)
  Mother; Just Plain Stupid; We'll Remember
- Health Care Workers Demonstration, 1992; 15 (Box 3)
  February 7, 1992; New York Coverage; (Schedule Enclosed)
- Local 1199, 1992; 16 (Box 3)
  Democratic National Convention; PBS-TV Network; July 14, 1992 -- 8:00-11:00 PM ET
- Dennis Rivera/Local 1199, 1992; 17 (Box 3)
  Tiempo; WABC-TV (ABC) New York; March 15, 1992 -- 8:00-8:30 AM
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 18 (Box 3)
  Charlie Rose; WNET-TV (PBS) New York; June 11, 1992 -- 11:00-12:00 AM
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199/Pataki, 1992; 19 (Box 3)
  Channel 2 News at Six; WCBS-TV (CBS) New York; March 14, 1995 -- 6:00-6:30 PM
- All News Coverage: October 2-4, 1989, 20 (Box 3)
  Contract Negotiations
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199/Summit of Idea, 1992; 21 (Box 3)
  Eyewitness News; WABC-TV (ABC) New York; December 14, 1992 -- 5:00-6:00 PM
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 22 (Box 3)
  Noticias; WXTV-TV (UNI) New York; July 15, 1992 -- 6:00-6:30 PM
- Dennis Rivera, 1994; 23 (Box 3)
  New York Up close; New York 1 Cable; July 21, 1994 -- 9:00-9:30 PM ET
- Local 1199, 1992; 24 (Box 3)
  Channel 9 News; Channel 11 News; Channel 2 News; Sunday Edition --- 3/21/1992
- Dennis Rivera, Local 1199, 1992; 1 (Box 4)
  News radio 88; CBS-AM New York (12/14/1992)